{
    "subject": "Eddie_Griffin",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Dysfunktional_Family",
    "human_readable": "Eddie Griffin created Dysfunctional Family.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7919862866401672,
            "question": "Has Eddie Griffin won any awards for his work on 'Dysfunctional Family'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6334397196769714,
            "question": "Who created the TV show 'Dysfunctional Family'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5036487579345703,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in 'Dysfunctional Family'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4569801986217499,
            "question": "What year was 'Dysfunctional Family' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4555182456970215,
            "question": "Does Eddie Griffin act in the show he created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39167484641075134,
            "question": "What type of program is 'Dysfunctional Family'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3214171230792999,
            "question": "What is the name of the TV show that Eddie Griffin created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3014068007469177,
            "question": "Is 'Dysfunctional Family' a comedy show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29613420367240906,
            "question": "Is Eddie Griffin known for creating television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2731860280036926,
            "question": "What other projects has Eddie Griffin been involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eddie Griffin created Dysfunctional Family.",
            "html": "yago_29789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Eddie Griffin known for creating television shows?",
            "html": "yago_29789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Dysfunctional Family' a comedy show?",
            "html": "yago_29789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the TV show that Eddie Griffin created?",
            "html": "yago_29789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29789_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your question:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that \"Eddie Griffin is widely known for his award winning Comedy Stand-up special Dysfunctional Family which he starred, wrote, Executive produced.\" This statement suggests that Eddie Griffin was involved in creating the comedy stand-up special called \"Dysfunctional Family\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Eddie Griffin starred, wrote, and executive produced a Comedy Stand-up special called \"Dysfunctional Family,\" which supports the statement that Eddie Griffin created \"Dysfunctional Family.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}